1,2,3,4
Scene
Ah.
White has 100 points
And white is 80 points
Yes, so this will be the second Sports Day project!
So, the first competition will be the chasing ball game!
I'm sorry, it's not "Oikakeri".
I'm sorry, it's "Oikakeri"!
The red group and the white group will choose an ogre each.
The ogre will carry a basket on his/her back.
This way, please.
There you go!
A basket.
It's new, isn't it?
He carries this basket on his back, like this.
Yes, sir.
And if it's the white team's turn to say, the red team tries to put it in this basket.
The number of balls in this basket x 10 points at the convenience store.
I've never done it before.
No, I haven't.
I've only played regular ball drop.
I see.
What do you think? I mean, don't you think that in junior high and high school, there's a ball drop or something like that at athletic meets?
No way.
Not so much of that, huh? Not anymore? That's not much of a thing, is it? Not anymore?
I had it when I was in elementary school, but not since I was in junior high or high school.
Not much has changed since then.
It's a bit unique, but I think it's important to choose the right demons.
I will do my best in the second round!
The one who bears first
The one who bears the burden
Then, the one who wins will be the one who bears the burden.
Ready, 3, 2, 1, jacket!
I'll carry it!
Oh!
Who's that?
Hey!
White first.
Congratulations.
I've got a plan. Can I try?
I'm the one who's supposed to carry the weight.
Well, let's do it.
The 8th, well, it's inevitable.
What's so important about this?
To move around.
And then I still don't care
How much I can get away without paying attention.
Can you move in 6 steps and average?
Oh, Kanna!
Two votes? Two votes?
Then I'll do it!
Yes, please.
Yes, sir.
Let's do it!
Sixteen hundred and sixty-three.
The best of the best are the strongest.
How's it going? Are you sure you can get away with this?
I'm not.
No!
You're last.
Number two.
What? When you see number 2...
Number 1?
One, two, three, four, five.
Which one is number four?
Yes, sir.
It's settled!
Yeah!
Excuse me, sir.
Now, let's start the chase ball game!
There it is!
Next notice Next Trailer
next preview
preview of the next episode
Yes!
I'm coming!
Come on!
You can do it!
I didn't say anything!
I can do it now!
Come on! It's okay! Yes!
Yes!
Good job!
Come on!
Like 해서 like
recorder
I'm here!
ana
Now let's count the points where we can finish
Thank you for your time.
Wait for me.
Now, follow me!
All right, let's get started! All right, let's get started!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Yay!
Yay! THIS IS ME off praise
Oh, my gosh!
Tekido, awesome, good
Tekido, awesome, good, good, good, good!
Floating place wouldn't
li
i
Thank you for your hard work.
It was sad.
Two copies of this commercial were released This commercial was released in two pieces
Black arrows
Thanks for watching this video.
congratulations!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
End
10 minutes later
Congratulations!
Potpourri also received a lot of hearts.
Next up is the jump rope!
The rule is that the number of times you can jump rope is your score.
If you get stuck, you can continue.
You will have 3 minutes to jump.
Okay.
How's it going?
Sorry.
It's so hard I want to withdraw.
No, because he's here.
You can't withdraw?
It's a test of teamwork.
It's a test of teamwork, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Which one of you would like to start first?
First, the winner gets to fly. First of all, the winner should fly this one.
Yes, sir.
First.
Winner flies.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
All right, let's go!
Yes, sir.
Sorry.
I'll start with the team again.
I'll start with red.
Start the big rope!
Ready?
Speech. Speech.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20
About 5 minutes!
Three, two, one.
Go for it, Yu-chan!
Take it, take it, take it, and the remaining number
thanks for your hard work!
ahaha
HIRO-chan
Cute
Cute Cute.
Looks like he cares.
That was Kitai.
Thanks for the caffeine car!
Good job everyone. Good job.
Now let's start the white team owner.
Seino!
Thank you for your hard work.
Properly!
Cool!
Great!
Still more!
That was awesome!
I've been on the road a long time.
It's 131.
The one I enjoyed the most was
Kiratotsubaki.
Awesome!!!
So I finished my second video!
I did the chasing ball game and the owner toby.
The total score now is 681 for red
White's total is 1072.
I'm in the time lead!
Oh no! Oh, man.
The next video is the last one.
That means this is going to be the final one.
I don't know up to this point.
In the next video, we're going to do an obstacle relay.
We're going to do two.
Each one is worth 300 points.
So...
We can't rule out the possibility of an upset.
White, too.
Red, 600 points.
There it is.
It's close.
That's not bad.
I want you to listen to something.
In the backstage video, Yohka got carried away and lost.
What do you mean?
Sorry, guys.
That's right.
She got carried away and lost.
That's what I meant.
Yeah. - Foreshadowing?
Foreshadowing?
Ahhh...
Yay!
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
It's all right.
I'm still waiting to see how this one ends.
Please look forward to the third video.
See you soon!
Bye-bye!
Jumping Power
I'd like to see it.
I can do it.
Yay!
Yay! Yay!